Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is extremely important to us. It is Kompas Production's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you on [SummertimeSaga.com](https://summertimesaga.com/). This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information collected and how we use it.

**Log Files.** When you go to the majority of web sites, the web server software logs your interaction in something called a log file. Standard log files like ours contain basic information like what time pages were viewed, browser used, and IP address. We use this information to administer the site, help debug errors, and track potential web based attacks against our infrastructure. We make no effort to identify IP addresses with individual users. These log files are periodically wiped.

**Cookies.** Our website does not directly make use of cookies.

**Cloudflare.** We use Cloudflare to help us optimize and protect our infrastructure. Cloudflare may place a cookie in your browser to provide its services. To learn more, Cloudflare's [Privacy & Security Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/).

**Google Fonts.** To help ensure uniform representation of fonts, we use Google's Font API. This service does not make use of any cookies. For more information about Google Fonts, their FAQ can be found [here](https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq), and privacy policy [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

**Third Party Links.** We may link to or embed from external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.

**Consent.** By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

_This policy is effective as of 12 August 2018._

© 2024 Kompas Productions. All Rights Reserved
